LORNA SUE BURNS

Leading Sales Professional

(425) 595-9264

https://thenerdsportfolio.tumblr.com/

courageousSecret@Gmail.com

-

6805 77th AVE NE Marysville, Washington 98270

MY PROFILE

A Valued face in the sales industry with over 4+ years of Sales and Customer service knowlage I have worked in many different feilds from Clothing all the way to hardware and chemical knowlage of paint and stains. I am someone who is more than determined to bring you a bang for your buck, not only would you be hiring an excelent sales professional you would also be hiring someone who has Graphic design knowlage and expertise so if organizational skills and a learned artistic creativity are what you need, I'm Your gal.

EDUCATION

2014-2018

ENTREPRENURSHIP

Getchell High School 2019 - Fall of 2021

Associates in

Graphic Design

Everett community Collage

SKILLS

Photoshop 3 Years

Illustrator 3 Years

Lightroom 3 Years

InDesign 2 Years

Microsoft Word 3 Years

Microsoft Excel 1 Year

Google Slides 2 Years

INTEREST

Acrylic and Watercolor painting

Reading and Writing

Dungeons and Dragons

Singing Karaoke

WORK EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE ARTIST

From Home

2020-Present

At the beginning of December I began to produce freelance work, Particularly on Fiverr and As a sample work for a previous company. I learned a few things as i have been working freelance;

- · Always ask questions & clarify misconceptions.
- To draft and thumbnail before any final product is worked on.
- Manage Time Wisely.
- Do not Take Work you cannot fit into your schedule.

PAINT SPECIALIST

Home Depot - 9310 Quil Ceda Blvd, Marysville, WA

2019 - 2020

Home Depot was a wonderful place to work both to learn as well as to just stop by to shop. The employees are caring and it was them that taught me that it's important to stop and talk to customers to understand what they need. A few other things I learned there were;

- Advanced color theory and Color Chemistry Via Tints and Bases
- Interior & Exterior design
- color matching
- the chemical makeup of paint, stains and epoxies.

SALES STAFF & CASHIER

Polo Ralph Lauren - 10600 Quil Ceda Blvd, Tulalip, WA

2018 - 2019

My first retail job, something I was hesitant with during the beginning but something I grew to love, it was quick work that taught me Cash Counting and management skills as well as how to manage during black friday, and general fashion knowlage. They also taught me other things.

- · Customer Interaction and Ettiquite
- · Arranging displays In such a way it is appealing to customers
- · Maintaining the store By cleaning, sweeping, and dusting.